http://www.cofchrist.org/privacy-policy

History
What We Offer (Video)
History
What We Offer (Video)
Privacy Policy
(last updated 11/11/2014)The privacy of your personal information is important to Community of Christ and our affiliated legal entities (collectively “we,” “us,” “our”). This privacy policy describes the current policies and practices with regard to how we collect, use, and process personal data collected through this website and all related websites (“Website”). The term "personal data" refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address, and any other information that identifies you personally.We strive to collect, use, and disclose personal data in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which we collect personal data. In selected jurisdictions, we may adopt unique privacy policy provisions to reflect the requirements of applicable local laws. When a separate provision is deemed necessary, we will provide you with an additional notice.In general, you can visit our Website without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Website, programs have been designed to perform specific functions for you directly though our Website. Within these programs we may ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. In some instances the information may include personal data.Your consentBy using the Website, you consent to our use of your personal data as described in this privacy policy.Notification of changes to this policyWe are continually improving and adding new functionality and features to the Website and improving and adding to its existing services and programs. Because of these ongoing changes, changes in the law, and the changing nature of technology, we may revise this privacy policy from time to time. If and when this policy changes, we will post the changes on the Website to notify you of the changes. We encourage you to check this page frequently.Use of personal data collected through this websiteThe only personal data we currently collect through the Website is the information you give us when you use our site. This includes, for example, the information you provide when you register for an event or conference, order resource materials, request other services, or when you send us your comments or requests for information.  Information, including but not limited to personal data, that we collect will not be sold, rented, lent, exchanged or used by an individual or entity other than us unless otherwise indicated. We use the information you provide for the purposes for which it was originally collected, for example, to respond to your email or to provide the programs or services you requested. We may also use this information to help us improve the content and functionality of our website, to better understand the needs and interests of the people and organizations that use the Website, and to improve our programs and services.  We may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about organizations, programs, services, and other things we believe will be of interest to you or to ask for your support.We may also share the personal data you provide to us with consultants and other third parties who act for or on behalf of Community of Christ, for further processing or analysis. In addition, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which Community of Christ may share or transfer the personal data in its databases, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or the Website, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.We, and others with whom we share your personal data, may retain your personal data on file to better serve you. Any destruction of personal data will be done in a manner consistent with the intent of this policy.Anonymous data collected through this websiteIn addition to the information you provide when you use this Website, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of the Website. For example, we use technology to track how many visitors access the Website, the date and time of their visit, the length of their stay, and which pages they view. We also use technology to determine which browsers our visitors use and the address from which they accessed the Website.This technology does not identify you personally. It simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our website. We use this anonymous data and may share it with third parties for various reasons; for example, to improve the content and functionality of the website, to better understand the needs and interests of our visitors, to improve our programs and services.CookiesIn order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use temporary "cookies" that collect the first level domain name of the user. For example, if your email address is "name@xyz.com," the cookie collects the "xyz.com" portion of your email address and the date and time you accessed this Web site. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. This enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not. Our Web site only uses temporary or "session" cookies. These "session" cookies expire when your browser window is closed.In order for certain applications on Community of Christ’s websites to function properly, if at all, it is necessary for your computer to accept cookies.Google AnalyticsCommunity of Christ uses some features of Google Analytics which does not collect any personal data but does obtain specific visitor, non-personal, cookie data, such as the source, medium and keyword used to visit the Website. Google Analytics does not store any visitor specific data and we will not disclose or share visitor specific data in any way related to Google Analytics.  Community of Christ and other third-party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together in order to gather such specific visitor, non-personal data based on your visits to the Website.ChildrenWe do not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen, please do not give us any personal data. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided personal data on this Website, please contact us and we will endeavor to delete that information. If you are a child under the age of thirteen and using this website, please do not give any information about yourself, such as your name, address, birth date, phone number, school or email address. We also strongly recommend that minors under the age of 18 ask their parents for permission before sending any personal information to anyone over the Internet, and we encourage parents to teach their children about safe Internet use practices.  As we develop online programs for children, we will adopt appropriate policies and practices to protect the privacy of children.Links to other sitesThis privacy policy applies only to this Web site. This site contains many hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by Community of Christ. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party Web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these websites and are not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or before providing any personal data about yourself.Governing lawThis privacy policy forms part of our Website’s Terms of Use and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Missouri.Questions About Our Privacy PolicyIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or concerns about the way we use personal data, please contact us by email, telephone or mail at:  Community of ChristAttn: Office of General Counsel 1001 W. WalnutIndependence, MO 64050legalservices@cofchrist.org  816-833-1000 ext. 2217
PrintFriendly
